ambank.com.my 2008-10-10

# AmOnline by AmBank

|  |   
  |  |  |   | 

AmOnline SECURITY & PRIVACY POLICY

|   
---  
AmOnline SECURITY & PRIVACY POLICY  
---  
   **Security Statement**  
   **Privacy Policy**  
   **Client Charter**  
  
**SECURITY STATEMENT**  
This Security Statement applies to the AmOnline Service ("AmBank Service"), owned and operated by AmBank (M) Berhad (Company No. 8515-D) (hereinafter referred to as "AmBank"). AmBank is committed to protect the privacy of your personal and financial information.

For the purposes herein, all words and expressions shall have the same meaning as in the Terms and Conditions for eChannel Services , except where otherwise expressly stated.

AmBank aims to maintain strict procedures and standards and take all reasonable care to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information, and to protect the security of your personal information during transmission. AmBank constantly monitors developments in security and encryption technology and will review and update its processes in line with industry standards.

AmBank has taken several security initiatives such as deploying technological hardware and software, policies and procedures, and addressing operational security issues.

The AmBank Service is secured with a digital certificate to enable safe communications with our customers. Such a feature ensures message privacy, web site authentication, and message integrity. You will be able to verify the website identity by clicking on the closed padlock icon located at the bottom of your browser window.  

Back to top  
**Your Obligations**

As a user, you play an important role in ensuring the security of your online banking sessions.

To secure the information transmitted between your personal computer and the AmBank Service, you will need Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.0 or higher or Netscape Communicator or Navigator 4.7 or higher with 128-bit encryption. Encryption is a mechanism of transmitting data in a secure way, where the data is encrypted using a key (this key is provided by a Certificate Authority (CA)).

To protect the privacy of your information, you are advised to remove the cache information using the steps provided below.

This Security Statement applies to the AmOnline Service ("AmBank Service"), owned and operated by AmBank (M) Berhad (Company No. 8515-D) (hereinafter referred to as "AmBank"). AmBank is committed to protect the privacy of your personal and financial information.

For the purposes herein, all words and expressions shall have the same meaning as in the Terms and Conditions for eChannel Services , except where otherwise expressly stated.

AmBank aims to maintain strict procedures and standards and take all reasonable care to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information, and to protect the security of your personal information during transmission. AmBank constantly monitors developments in security and encryption technology and will review and update its processes in line with industry standards.

AmBank has taken several security initiatives such as deploying technological hardware and software, policies and procedures, and addressing operational security issues.

The AmBank Service is secured with a digital certificate to enable safe communications with our customers. Such a feature ensures message privacy, web site authentication, and message integrity. You will be able to verify the website identity by clicking on the closed padlock icon located at the bottom of your browser window.  

Back to top  
**Login ID / Password**

Personal information supplied by you through the AmBank Service shall be used in providing AmBank's services. AmBank may also use your personal information to market AmBank Group's products and services to you based on your interests and to mainly assist AmBank Group in customising and delivering its services and products that may be of interest to you.

AmBank will not use or disclose information collected about you, including information collected using cookies, other than for the purpose made known to you, a purpose you would reasonably expect, a purpose required, authorised or permitted by or under law, or a purpose otherwise authorised by you.

You agree that AmBank shall not disclose your personal information unless the following circumstances apply:

 _Authentication_  
Your ATM card number, Web Pin and identification number will be used to authenticate you for the AmOnline Service during the enrolment process.

Your Login ID and Password will be used to authenticate you for the AmOnline Service during subsequent logins. To ensure the integrity of your Login ID and Password, AmBank advises you to periodically change your Password and under no circumstances should you reveal your Password to anyone. You should not disclose your Password to AmBank's personnel even if requested to do so.  
When selecting a Password, do not associate your selected Password with anything personal such as names, birth dates, phone numbers or other familiar words.

 _Account Locking_  
Attempts to impersonate valid users are locked by AmBank's system after five (5) incorrect sign-on attempts. _Automatic Log Out_  
If there is inactivity of three (3) minutes during your AmOnline session, AmBank's system will automatically log you out of the system. You are then required to re-login.  

Back to top  
**Data Security & Confidentiality**

AmBank, in its goal to protect the privacy and security of your information, has implemented the following security features:

  * Personal Identification Number Verification
  * Login ID and Password Verification 
  * Encryption of Passwords
  * Firewalls & Intrusion Detection Systems
  * Anti-Virus Application
  * Internal Policies & Guidelines
  * Periodic Penetration Testing
  * Server side Authentication through Digital Certificates

The AmBank Service is designed to give you control over your financial information. AmBank uses the industry standard security measures available through your browser that is known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. To ensure that your financial information is kept secure, AmBank stores it on a data repository in a secured data centre.  

Back to top  
**Firewalls & Intrusion Detection Systems**

Firewalls act as filters that prevent information from getting in or out of a protected network. AmBank also has an intrusion detection system to automatically disable attacks from hackers. The intrusion detection system alerts AmBank's security personnel about possible attacks-in-progress and AmBank keeps audit logs to provide a trail of information.  

Back to top  
**Internal Policies & Guidelines**

AmBank adopts various policies and procedures for managing system access, system back-ups and other operations management to safeguard access to AmBank's systems. Several guidelines and procedures have been put in place to minimise the potential security breaches and to ensure and protect the data integrity of AmBank's network.  

Back to top  
**Anti Virus Application**

With the outbreak of viruses over the Internet, it is critical for AmBank to have anti-virus applications. AmBank has implemented industry standard anti-virus applications to ensure its systems are safe from viruses. For you to have safe and secure Internet banking sessions, you should ensure that you have implemented anti-virus software on your personal computer for added protection.  

Back to top  
**Enquiries and Complaints**

Always remember to log off or log out after you have completed your online banking session. If you suspect any unusual account activity, please contact AmBank immediately using the contact information provided below.  

Back to top  
**How To Remove Cache Information - Steps To Protect The Privacy Of Your Information**

Steps to clear cache according to your respective internet browser.

 _Internet Explorer 7_  

  1. From the "Tools" menu, select "Internet Options".
  2. Select the "General" tab.
  3. Under Browsing history, click "Delete".
  4. Next to "Temporary Internet Files", click "Delete files".
  5. Click "Close", and then click "OK" to exit.

_Internet Explorer 4.x, 5.x, and 6.x for Windows_  

  1. From the "Tools" menu (for version 4.x, the "View" menu), select "Internet Options".
  2. Select the "General" tab.
  3. In the "Temporary Internet Files" section, click "Delete Files".
  4. To confirm the deletion, click "OK".
  5. In the Internet Options dialog box, select "OK".

_Netscape 8 for Windows_  

  1. From the "Tools" menu, select "Options".
  2. Click "Privacy".
  3. Next to "Cache", click the "Clear" button.
  4. If you'd like to set the size of the cache and set the browser to clear the cache when you close it, click the + (plus sign) next to "Cache" and change the settings as needed.
  5. Click "OK".

_Netscape 7.1 for Windows_  

  1. From the "Edit" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. In the left panel of the Preferences dialog box, click the + (plus sign) in the box to the left of "Advanced". Click "Cache".
  3. Click "Clear Cache".
  4. In the Preferences dialog box, click "OK".

_Netscape Navigator 4.x, 6.x, and 7.0 for Windows_  

  1. From the "Edit" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. In the left panel of the Preferences dialog box, click the + (plus sign) in the box to the left of "Advanced". Click "Cache".
  3. Click "Clear Memory Cache". Confirm by clicking "OK".
  4. Click "Clear Disk Cache". Confirm by clicking "OK".
  5. In the Preferences dialog box, click "OK".

_Firefox 2.0 for Windows_  

  1. From the "Tools" menu, select "Clear Private Data", and then Select "Cache".

_Firefox 1.0 and 1.5 for Windows_  

  1. From the "Tools" menu, select "Options", and then click "Privacy".
  2. In 1.5, select the "Cache" tab, and then click the "Clear Cache Now" button. In 1.0, next to "Cache", click the "Clear" button, and then click "OK".

_Safari_  

  1. From the "Safari" menu, select "Empty Cache".
  2. When prompted, click "Empty" to confirm that you want to empty the cache.

_Firefox 1.0 and 1.5 for Mac OS X_  

  1. From the "Firefox" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. From the sheet that drops down, select "Privacy". In 1.5, click "Clear Cache Now". In 1.0, next to "Cache", click the "Clear" button, and then "OK".

_Netscape 6.x or later and Mozilla for Mac OS and Mac OS X_  

  1. In Mac OS X, from the Netscape or Mozilla menu, select "Preferences". In Mac OS 9.x or earlier, from the "Edit" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. In the left panel of the Preferences dialog box, click the arrow to the left of "Advanced". Click "Cache".
  3. Either click the "Clear Cache" button, or click both the "Clear Memory Cache" and "Clear Disk Cache" buttons.
  4. In the Preferences dialog box, click "OK".

_Netscape Navigator 4.x for Mac OS_  

  1. From the "Edit" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. In the left panel, click the arrow to the left of "Advanced".
  3. Click "Cache".
  4. Click "Clear Disk Cache Now", then click "OK". Click "OK" again.

_Internet Explorer 4.x and 5.x for Mac OS and Mac OS X_

Note: Microsoft is no longer developing or distributing Internet Explorer for the Macintosh. UITS strongly recommends that you use a different browser, such as Safari or Firefox. 

  1. In Mac OS X, from the "Explorer" menu, select "Preferences". In Mac OS 9.x and earlier, from the "Edit" menu, select "Preferences".
  2. In the left panel, click the arrow to the left of "Web Browser". Click the "Advanced" button.
  3. Under "Cache", click "Empty Now", then click "OK".

Back to top  
**PRIVACY POLICY**  
**About this Privacy Policy Statement**

This privacy policy statement applies to the AmBank Group's web site located at www.ambg.com.my ("AmBank Group site") and www.AmOnline.com.my ("AmOnline Portal"), owned and operated by AmBank (M) Berhad (8515-D).

By using or accessing the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal, you shall be deemed to have accepted this Privacy Policy Statement ("this Statement"). If you do not accept this Statement, please immediately discontinue your access to the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal.

AmBank Group reserves the right to change the contents and/or services offered on the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal including this Statement at any time and without notice. By your continued use or access of the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal you shall be deemed to have agreed to and accepted the changes in this Statement. You are advised to periodically review this Statement for changes.

In addition to this Statement, specific privacy provisions may apply to certain sections of the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal. These specific privacy provisions must be read together with this Statement. In the event of any inconsistency between this Statement and the specific provisions, the specific provisions shall prevail.

For the purposes herein, all words and expressions shall have the same meaning as in the Terms of Use, except where otherwise expressly stated.  

Back to top  
**Collection of Personal Information**

The AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal are committed to ensure the privacy of its users. The information collected by AmBank Group about you will depend on how you use the facilities and features on the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal.

When you use the AmOnline, the information collected will generally include your Login ID, Password, personally identifiable information, contact details and identification numbers. This information is necessary for us to provide the service you applied for. Personal information provided by you upon application for the AmOnline shall be used to enroll you for the AmBank Contact Centre.

To enable us to monitor the activity on the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal, we also collect information such as the number of users, the date and time of visits, the number of pages viewed and the information downloaded. In addition to this, we collect personal information when you use the online application forms to apply for our products and/or services and when you complete the survey forms or contact/feedback forms available on the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal.  

Back to top  
**Use and Disclosure of Information**

Personal information supplied by you through the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal shall be used in providing AmBank Group's services. AmBank Group may also use your personal information to market AmBank Group's products and services to you based on your interests and to mainly assist AmBank Group in customising and delivering its services and products that may be of interest to you.

AmBank Group will not use or disclose information collected about you, including information collected using cookies, other than for the purpose made known to you, a purpose you would reasonably expect, a purpose required, authorised or permitted by or under law, or a purpose otherwise authorised by you.

You agree that AmBank Group shall not disclose your personal information unless the following circumstances apply:

  * for the purpose of processing your Instruction(s) given through the AmOnline;
  * when cross selling and cross servicing the products and/or services of AmBank Group; and/or
  * to any third party service providers, contractors, agents who provide administrative, telecommunication, computer payment or securities clearing or other services to AmBank Group in connection with the operation of its business. In such cases, AmBank Group will require that such persons undertake to keep your information confidential.

Although AmBank Group uses reasonable efforts to ensure that third parties keep your information confidential, please be informed that AmBank Group has no control over these third parties, who may or may not further disclose information to other parties and there can be no assurances that such parties will not solicit you via e-mail or otherwise.

Demographic or statistical information collated from any information provided by you upon your use of the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal may be divulged to any third party. Such demographic or statistical information shall be in the form of a summary or compilation of information, which is not personally identifiable.

If you do not wish to be solicited for products or services offered by AmBank Group, please indicate accordingly when requested.  

Back to top  
**Information Security**

You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your Login ID and Password for the AmOnline. AmBank Group will not be able to secure your information if you reveal your Login ID and Password to anyone. AmBank Group's personnel are not authorised to ask you for your Password.

For the AmOnline, AmBank Group applies stringent procedures to ensure that only a limited number of authorised personnel within the organisation will have direct access to your personal data. Transmission of data during login, registration and personal information update between the browser and server in the AmOnline is encrypted using the proven 128-bit Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology.

All your personal data collected from the AmOnline is stored in secured repositories in our secured data centre. Only authorised personnel have physical access to the data repositories in limited circumstances and they are prohibited from making any unauthorised disclosure of your personal data. Backups are performed to ensure that your personal information is safe against system failures. These backups are stored in a secured location.

AmBank Group takes reasonable care to ensure that the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal are safe and secure, however please be informed that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as fully secure. As such, AmBank Group cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you send to us through the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal. You submit information at your own risk. Once AmBank Group receives your information, AmBank Group will take all reasonable steps to protect the data held in its system.  

Back to top  
**Your access to your Personal Information**

AmBank Group regards confidentiality and privacy of your information of paramount importance. Upon request, we may provide you access to the personal information we hold about you. The information will be limited to your address, occupation, age, sex, martial status, accounts with us and the balances and statements relating to those accounts. You can also inform AmBank Group in writing of any changes or errors in your personal information and AmBank Group will update its records or correct any errors as soon as possible as to ensure accuracy and completeness of your personal information.  

Back to top  
**Use of "cookies"**

The AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal may send you a "cookie". A cookie is a package of data that allows our server to identify and interact more effectively with your computer without identifying the individual users. Most current browser programmes can be configured to refuse, reject or delete such cookies.  

Back to top  
**Links to other Sites**

The AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal may be linked to other web sites but AmBank Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of these linked sites. AmBank Group advises you to read the privacy practices of those linked sites.  

Back to top  
**Enquiries and Complaints**

You may address any queries, concerns or complaints regarding the use of your personal information or this Statement, using the contact information provided below.

Contact Information:  
      AmBank Contact Centre  
      P.O. Box No. 12617  
      50784 Kuala Lumpur.  
      E-mail address: customercare@ambg.com.my  

Back to top  
**CLIENT CHARTER**  
We, at AmBank Group, are committed to ensuring security, confidentiality and convenience when delivering our financial products and services to you on our website located at www.ambg.com.my ("AmBank Group site") and www. AmOnline.com.my ("AmOnline Portal").

As our customer, you now have access to our AmOnline which makes it easier and more convenient to undertake financial transactions. With the convenience of the new and effective delivery channel via the Internet, we shall be able to deliver our financial services more effectively in terms of speed, reliability and quality.  

Back to top  
**Security**

The security of our AmOnline portal is foremost in our commitment to you.

Security measures such as data encryption, server authentication and firewalls, combined with our strict internal security procedures and policies, are some of the security measures that we employ to ensure that you may use our AmOnline securely and safely. Our security measures are continuously being monitored and reviewed in our endeavor to benefit from the latest security technologies available. For further details please read our Security Statement.  

Back to top  
**Privacy**

We take all reasonable precautionary measures to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or unauthorised access. For more information, please see our Privacy Policy Statements.  

Back to top  
**Accuracy**

The contents of the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal are updated and reviewed from time to time in our endeavor to maintain its correctness for your enjoyment and convenience.  

Back to top  
**Convenience**

Our online products and services are provided primarily for your convenience. Towards this end, we are constantly innovating and creating new and exciting products and services so that we may serve you better.  

Back to top  
**Enquiries and Suggestions**

We trust you will find the AmBank Group site and AmOnline portal easy and convenient to use, and our contents useful and interesting. We welcome feedback, enquiries and suggestions to assist us in improving our services to you.

You may address your queries or suggestions by contacting us using the contact information given below and we shall use our best efforts to promptly attend to your queries.

Contact Information:  
      AmBank Contact Centre  
      P.O. Box No. 12617  
      50784 Kuala Lumpur.  
      E-mail address: customercare@ambg.com.my   

Back to top  

  |   
|  |  This website is brought to you by eChannel, AmBank (M) Berhad   
---|---  
  |  |   |   
   
|  |
